dear potential patreon supporter and
whether you're new to my work or whether
you've been drawing from my work for the
last three four years or longer now is a
special moment in my personal life but
also on a planetary scale that a lot of
us have to reconsider how they do their
work and I basically have just had my
income slashed by about seventy five
percent and that income is supported
probably me working more than half of my
time for free for many organizations but
also doing the work I do online sharing
things so this is really a call to all
of you to who can afford it because I
know many of you are in similar
situations or much worse those of you
who can afford it and have appreciated
my working can still afford to maybe put
a standing order to support one of the
six tiers I've set up on patreon I would
really ask you to consider where they
can do that because I would love to be
able to continue to do my work and I
will try to do my best anyway to do so
but right now is really the time where I
need a little bit of support and that
can come in different ways from monthly
donations that range from ten to twenty
to fifty to a hundred to two hundred and
even to five hundred euros a month and
if you look at the page you can see
these six tiers are structured with a
couple of little return gift offers but
really what I'm asking you is to support
me to keep doing what I'm doing and if
you feel that that is valuable and that
you can afford to support it then
consider it and otherwise please keep
drawing from the material and I will not
hide stuff behind paywalls
because I want these ideas to travel and
I want to support the regeneration
rising everywhere as much as possible
I don't pretend I've never pretended to
have answers but I have lots of
questions and I've done a lot of work
over the last 20 years looking at how we
might participate more appropriately in
this nested wholeness that is us in that
we depend upon or we can create
community resilience how we can
regenerate by the regional economies and
restore local ecosystems and how
ultimately can heal the planet and in
the course heal ourselves that is really
what I'm dedicated to it and what I
continue to do now but now has come the
time where if you can please consider
supporting it so thank you very much and
take a look at the letter and the six
possible ways of supporting me and just
sharing my work as already supporting me
and reading it is nourishing me to see
how many people come back and actually
draw meaning and inside and new guidance
from the things that I've just pulled
together from other people's work and
honoring the network and making the
network visible so please I'm deeply
grateful if you could help a little bit
thank you bye